<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE glossary [
<!-- in PDF: for line 1 on the cover page -->
<!ENTITY PRODNAME "Rackspace Autoscale"> 
<!-- in PDF: for page headers -->
<!ENTITY PRODABBV "Rackspace Autoscale"> 
<!-- in body -->
<!ENTITY PROD "Autoscale">               
]>
<glossary 
    xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
    xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" version="5.0"
    xml:id="Glossary-000">
    <title>Glossary</title>
    <glossentry xml:id="Authentication-d1e01">
        <glossterm><emphasis role="bold">Authentication</emphasis></glossterm>
        <glossdef>
            <para>
                Authentication is the act or process of confirming the identity of a
                <link linkend="User-d1e15">user</link> or the truth of a claim.
                The authentication service confirms that an incoming request is being made by the user
                who claims to be making the request.
                It does this by validating a set of claims that the user makes.
                These claims are initially in the form of a set of <link linkend="Credentials-d1e03">credentials</link>.
                After initial confirmation based on credentials,
                the authentication service issues a <link linkend="Token-d1e13">token</link> to the user;
                when making subsequent requests,
                the user can provide the token
                as evidence that the user's identity has already been authenticated.
            </para>
        </glossdef>
    </glossentry>
    <glossentry xml:id="Credentials-d1e03">
        <glossterm><emphasis role="bold">Credentials</emphasis></glossterm>
        <glossdef>
            <para>
                Credentials are data that belong to and identify a specific <link linkend="User-d1e15">user</link>.
                Because credentials are assumed to be known by only one user, users who present valid
                credentials are assumed to have proven that they are who they say they are.
                Examples of credentials include:
                <itemizedlist spacing="compact">
                    <listitem><para>a matching username and password</para></listitem>
                    <listitem><para>a matching username and API key</para></listitem>
                    <listitem><para>a unique token</para></listitem>
                </itemizedlist>
            </para>
        </glossdef>
    </glossentry>
    <glossentry xml:id="Service_Catalog-d1e10">
        <glossterm><emphasis role="bold">Service Catalog</emphasis></glossterm>
        <glossdef>
            <para>
                Your service catalog is the list of services available to you, as returned along with your authentication
                <link linkend="Token-d1e13">token</link> and an expiration date for that token.
                All the services in your service catalog should recognize your token as valid until it expires.
            </para>
            <para>
                The catalog listing for each service provides at least one endpoint URL for that service.
                Other information, such as regions and versions and tenants, is provided if it's relevant to your access to this service.
            </para>
        </glossdef>
    </glossentry>
    <glossentry xml:id="Sub-User-d1e20">
        <glossterm><emphasis role="bold">Sub-User</emphasis></glossterm>
        <glossdef>
            <para> A sub-user, also called a sub-account, is a
                child of the account's fully-privileged administrative
                user. Each account has exactly one administrative
                user, holding the <code>identity:user-admin</code>
                role; optionally, one or multiple sub-users can be
                created, each holding the
                <code>identity:default</code> role. Each sub-user
                shares its parent's tenant information, group
                memberships, and endpoints. </para>
        </glossdef>
    </glossentry>
    <glossentry xml:id="Tenant-d1e11">
        <glossterm><emphasis role="bold">Tenant</emphasis></glossterm>
        <glossdef>
            <para>
                A tenant is a container used to group or isolate resources and/or identity
                objects. Depending on the service operator, a tenant may map to a customer,
                account, organization, or project.
            </para>
        </glossdef>
    </glossentry>
    <glossentry xml:id="Token-d1e13">
        <glossterm><emphasis role="bold">Token</emphasis></glossterm>
        <glossdef>
            <para>
                A token is an opaque string that represents an authorization to access cloud
                resources. Tokens may be revoked at any time and are valid for a finite duration.
            </para>
        </glossdef>
    </glossentry>
    <glossentry xml:id="User-d1e15">
        <glossterm><emphasis role="bold">User</emphasis></glossterm>
        <glossdef>
            <para>
                A user is a digital representation of a person, system, or service who consumes cloud services.
                Users have credentials and may be assigned tokens; based on these credentials and tokens,
                the authentication service validates that incoming requests are being made by the user
                who claims to be making the request, and that the user has the right to access the requested resources.
                Users may be directly assigned to a particular tenant and
                behave as if they are contained within that tenant.
            </para>
        </glossdef>
    </glossentry>
</glossary>
